genuinejobs.com 2011-12-31

# Privacy Genuinejobs.com

Privacy Policy

* * *

We've created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for this website: **Genuinejobs.com.**  

The bottom line is, we value your privacy and never, ever give out your email or any other personal information without your consent. We are not in the business of selling our visitors' information.

Why did you receive an email from us?

If you received a mailing from us, (a) your email address is either listed with us as someone who has expressly shared this address for the purpose of receiving information in the future ("opt-in"), or (b) you have registered or purchased or otherwise have an existing relationship with us. We respect your time and attention by controlling the frequency of our mailings.

How we protect your privacy

We use security measures to protect against the loss, misuse and alteration of data used by our system. 

Sharing and Usage

We will never share, sell, or rent individual personal information with anyone without your advance permission or unless ordered by a court of law. Information submitted to us is only available to employees managing this information for purposes of contacting you or sending you emails based on your request for information and to contracted service providers for purposes of providing services relating to our communications with you.

How can you stop receiving email from us?

Each email sent contains an easy, automated way for you to cease receiving email from us, or to change your expressed interests. If you wish to do this, simply follow the instructions at the end of any email email received.

If you have received unwanted, unsolicited email(s) sent via this system or purporting to be sent via this system, please forward a copy of that email with your comments to [abuse@genuinejobs.com](mailto:abuse@genuinejobs.com) for review.

This site contains links to other sites. **Genuinejobs.com** is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites.

IP Address

When you are connected to the Internet, your computer has a unique Internet ID called an IP address. When you submit a registration request for the free ezine, your IP address may be logged to confirm your interest for security reasons.

Notification of Changes

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post these changes on this page so that you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose it. Regardless of later updates, we will never use the information you submit under this current policy in a new way without first providing you an opportunity to opt-out or otherwise prevent that use.
